Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Morning rush, the grinders home, another day has just begun.
Steam swells up a hazy dream
Serving coffee, a gentle stream
Faces blur a hurried pace
Finding beauty in this place
A quick glance at the clocks off chime
Stealing moments, stealing time
My notebook hidden out of sight
Waiting for the fading light in this cafe
I pour the brew but my heart dreams of something new
A writer's soul a hidden art
Playing out a different part
Beneath the surface words take flight
Chasing stories, day and night
Lattice foam, a creamy art
Each cup of beat within my heart
A quiet smile, a whispered thanks
Building bridges, building banks of tiny moments
Pure and true, reflected in the morning dew
The afternoon begins to fade
My inner world a serenade
Versus waiting to be spun
Until the working day is done
In this cafe I pour the brew but my heart dreams of something new
A writer's soul a hidden art
Playing out a different part
Beneath the surface words take flight
Chasing stories, day and night
Maybe one day the world will see
The hidden poet inside of me
These daily scenes a source of grace
Finding rhythm in this space
The last customer a gentle sigh
As shadows lengthen in the sky
I wipe the counter lock the door
And long for something something more
My pen is ready pages white to capture feelings
Burning bright in this cafe
I pour the brew but my heart dreams of something new
A writer's soul a hidden art
Playing out a different part
Beneath the surface words take flight
Chasing stories, day and night